pixsta.com 2013-12-20

# Pokki Privacy Policy 2013-07-03 FINAL

Pokki Privacy Policy

Pokki, Inc. (“we” or “Pokki”) understands that you care about your privacy, and we take your privacy seriously. To inform you about the ways your information may be collected and used, we have adopted this Pokki Privacy Policy, which describes what types of information we collect, how we may use such information, with whom we may share such information, the choices you can make, and how you can contact us about our privacy practices.  

1.     WHAT OUR POKKI PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

This Pokki Privacy Policy covers our treatment of information we collect when you are accessing our Pokki-related website(s) owned and operated by Pokki (the “Pokki Site” or “Pokki Sites”).  Such Pokki Sites include [http://www.pokki.com](http://www.pokki.com/), [http://www.tweeki.com](http://www.tweeki.com/), [http://www.inst.ag](http://www.inst.ag/) and our store (the “Pokki App Store”), a publicly available app marketplace located at www.pokki.com (or such other site operated by Pokki), and/or integrated with the Pokki Software (as defined below).  

This Pokki Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of information we collect when you use any of our Pokki-related services or products, including installing or using a web-connected desktop application utilizing the Pokki platform (a “Pokki App” or “Pokki Apps”), including the app management, discovery and notification menu built within the Pokki platform (the “Pokki Menu”) (the Pokki Apps and the Pokki Menu, collectively the “Pokki Software”).

By visiting our Pokki Sites, using Pokki Software, or using any of our Pokki-related services or products, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Pokki Privacy Policy.

Please note this policy does not apply to (and we are not responsible for) the practices of companies that we do not own or control or to individuals we do not employ or manage. When utilizing third party sites or software products, including Pokki Apps that may be provided by third parties, or Pokki Software or Pokki Sites that access or utilize third party sites or services, you should read the relevant privacy policies of those third parties for information regarding their privacy practices.

2.     SUMMARY OF OUR POKKI PRIVACY POLICY

Pokki maintains or provides multiple Pokki-related sites, products and services.  To better explain what information we collect, and how we use the information we collect, we have broken out our Pokki Privacy Policy into the following sections: 

                Section 3:  WHAT WE COLLECT AND WHY.  This section explains what information we collect from: (a) users who install Pokki Software; (b) Pokki App developers and publishers; and (c) visitors to our Pokki Sites, including the Pokki App Store. 

                Section 4:  HOW WE SHARE OR USE INFORMATION WE HAVE COLLECTED.  This section explains how we use your information, and why, as well as if and how we share your information. 

                Sections 5-10:  These sections discuss various topics, including how we protect any information we collect, your rights and choices, our compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, our storage and use of information from users outside the United States, how we may alert you of any changes to this Pokki Privacy Policy, and how you can contact us.   

3.     WHAT WE COLLECT AND WHY

Cookies. When you visit our Pokki Sites, we will send you a cookie, which is a small file stored on your computer that allows us to uniquely identify it. Where required by applicable law, we obtain your consent for the use of cookies.  You may choose to delete or not accept our cookies as described under “Your Rights and Choices” below.  If you delete or choose not to accept our cookies, you may not be able to utilize all the features of our products and services.  

Logs. When you install Pokki Software, or when you visit our Pokki Sites, we capture and store the data that your computer or web browser sends us. This data may include your operating system (OS) type, browser type, language, Internet Protocol (IP) address, the date and time of your request and the cookie ID (when you visit our Pokki Sites) or unique ID (when you install Pokki Software) that helps identify your computer. We may also determine your geographical information through your IP address to better understand the interaction of your location with your use of our Pokki Software and Pokki Sites.  However, we do not store or associate your IP address with any data we collect from you, and we only collect and store geographical information we have derived in aggregate form.    

Usage Information. Generally, our Pokki Software automatically collects usage information with respect to particular Pokki Apps, or with respect to the Pokki Menu, such as the frequency with which a Pokki App or the Pokki Menu has been clicked or opened, and how long a Pokki App or Pokki Menu remains open. We also collect installation information, which may include information on whether a Pokki App or the Pokki Menu has been installed or uninstalled, and how long the Pokki Software has been installed on your system.  

With respect to visitors to the Pokki Sites, we collect usage information such as the number and frequency of visitors, what pages have been visited, average time spent on pages, and other information which helps us determine which features on our Pokki Sites are most important to you and working effectively.  

We only use the usage information we collect in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure to allow us to improve the Pokki platform.  We do not use such usage information to identify you, nor do we associate any usage information we collect with any information that may personally identify you, such as a name or address.    

Third Party Analytic Tools.  The Pokki Site, the Pokki Menu, and the Pokki Apps that we have developed, may use third party analytic tools that use cookies, web beacons, or other similar information gathering technologies to collect standard internet log information and usage information.  The information generated is used to compile statistical reports on user activity.  We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical reports to track or to collect any personal information of visitors to the Pokki Sites or users of Pokki software. We will not associate any information gathered from the statistical reports with any personal information from any source.    

User Accounts.  If you have created a user account, we collect and maintain all information that you provide to us in connection with your creation of a Pokki user account, including personal information such as your name, email address, date of birth and photo (if you have chosen to upload a photo to your user account profile). The personal information you provide in connection with your account is used in order to help us manage your account and provide services and features in connection with your account.  We never associate any personal information you provide in connection with your account with any other information we may collect through the Pokki Sites or the Pokki Software.  

Third Party Pokki Apps and Sites.  If you have installed a Pokki App provided by a third party, or a Pokki App that accesses third party sites or services, then that third party may also collect information regarding your usage of such Pokki App, or your access or usage of the third party sites or services accessed by such Pokki App.  Any information collected by a third party provider of a Pokki App, or a site or service accessed by a Pokki App, is governed by such third party providers’ privacy policies.  These third party sites or applications may also place their own cookies or other files on your computer, or may collect data or solicit personal information from you.  We do not exercise control over any third party sites that a Pokki App or other third party application, may link to.

Software Developer Accounts. If you are a software developer or publisher that uses the Pokki.com site to publish or distribute your Pokki App, we collect and maintain all information that you provide to us in connection with the Pokki App submission, review and approval process in order to help us manage your account and communicate with you regarding our review of a submitted Pokki App.

Communications; Other Information You Provide.  Any time you send us a communication, whether as a posting to our support pages, through email inquiries, or via postings or communications on social media sites or networks such as Facebook or Twitter, we may keep such communications so that we can respond to your requests or inquiries and help improve our services to you.  Posts to our Support pages located within support.pokki.com will display your user name as you have indicated it in your profile. The personal information you provide is used for such purposes as improving the content of our sites, customizing and improving our services, and communicating with you about our services.  We may use personal information you provide to communicate with you about specials and new features.  We will obtain your consent where required by applicable law.  You can opt out from receiving promotional communications at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions described in the email.

4.     HOW WE USE OR SHARE INFORMATION WE HAVE COLLECTED

a.     For Pokki App Users Without a User Account. 

We only use the information we collect from Pokki Software users without an account in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you, in order to allow us to improve the Pokki platform.  We do not sell or otherwise market this information to third parties. 

For Pokki App Users With a User Account. 

If you have created a user account and have posted information on a leaderboard or reviewed a Pokki App, your first name and photo (if you have chosen to upload a photo to your user account profile) will be displayed with your review or leaderboard information on the Pokki Site or within the pertinent Pokki App.  If you have created a user account and have shared a Pokki App with another user, your first name and photo (if one has been uploaded to your user account profile) will be shared with users with which you have chosen to share a Pokki App.  In addition, we may use the email address you provided to communicate to you about products, services and promotions.  We may use your date of birth to verify your eligibility to use our services in accordance with our Terms of Use.  

b.     For Pokki App Developers and Publishers.  

We may share your personal information with third party service providers for the purpose of approving and enabling your participation in the Pokki App Store. For example, processing and approving your Pokki App submissions, email, analyzing data, and providing other partner services. Our service providers do not have any right to use personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us and perform services on our behalf.  We require these service providers by contract to appropriately safeguard the privacy and security of personal information they process on our behalf.

c.     For All Information We Collect.  We may also use or share your information as follows: 

         Protection of Pokki and Others. We may share your personal information if we have a good faith belief that it is required to: (1) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order; (2) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (3) enforce the provisions of this Pokki Privacy Policy and/or any other agreements between you and Pokki, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or (4) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Pokki, its visitors, users and/or the public.

         Business Transfers. If Pokki or substantially all of its assets are acquired, or in the unlikely event that Pokki goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that would be transferred to, or acquired by, a third party acquiror. Accordingly, we may transfer or assign all the information we have collected as part of a merger, acquisition, sale or other change of control. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that we will use reasonable efforts to direct any acquiror to continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

       Usage Information. We may share usage information that we collect with partners and other third parties for the purpose of helping us improve the Pokki platform and the overall performance of our products and services, or allow us to provide recommendations. For example, utilizing data to determine the probability that a consumer will enjoy a specific Pokki App or product.  We do not authorize these partners and other third parties to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform certain services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements.  We require them by contract to appropriately safeguard the privacy and security of the information they process in assisting us.  

         With Your Consent. Except as set forth above, we will only share your personal information with third parties with your prior consent.  If our business practices change in a way that we would need to share your personal information for purposes that are not compatible with the purposes for which we collected the information, we will ask for your additional consent.  

         Marketing. We may use your personal information to send you marketing communications.  We will obtain your consent where required by applicable law.  

 5.     INFORMATION SECURITY

We endeavor to take reasonable and appropriate security measures to guard against unauthorized access to the systems where we store your personal information. This includes technical and organizational measures such as internal reviews of our data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical and electronic security measures in compliance with applicable security requirements. In addition, we authorize access to personal information only for those of our employees who require it to fulfill their job responsibilities.  However, despite the measures we take we cannot warrant the security of any information provided to us. 

6.     YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES

Through the process provided on our site, we allow you to access certain information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. The types of information that you can access and update may change as our site changes. You may also contact us as set forth in the “Contact” section below to request access to, or update, your personal information.

You may request deletion of your account by sending an e-mail to [help@pokki.com](mailto:help@pokki.com) and responding affirmatively to any confirmation e-mails that we may send. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.  

If you are a user of our Pokki Sites, you also have the choice to stop accepting new cookies, to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and to disable existing cookies by using the privacy settings of your browser.  All major browsers allow you to block or delete cookies from your system. Please refer to the help section of your browser for more information.

Where we have requested your consent to use or share your personal information, you have the right to withdraw such consent, however, you may no longer be able to benefit from certain products and services. In addition, you may opt-out from receiving marketing communications from us, for example, by clicking on the relevant link included in such e-mail communications. 

7.     CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we will not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13.  We encourage parents and guardians to be familiar with the websites that their children visit.  The Federal Trade Commission ("FTC") regulates the means by which website operators collect and use personal information from children under 13, pursuant to COPPA.  For more information about COPPA and children's on-line privacy in general, visit the FTC's website at www.ftc.gov/privacy.  For safety tips on privacy visit [www.OnGuardOnline.gov](http://www.onguardonline.gov/).

8.     TRANSFERS

Our Pokki Sites, Pokki Apps, Pokki Menu, and other services and products are hosted by servers located in the United States.  If you are located outside the United States, your information will be transferred to our servers in the United States.  The United States may not have the same privacy and data protection laws as the country in which you are located when you are using our products and services. When we transfer your information to the United States, we will protect that information as described in this Pokki Privacy Policy. If you are located in the European Economic Area, or other regions of the world with laws governing international data transfers, we comply with applicable legal requirements such as to ensure adequate protection for data transfers.  By visiting our Pokki Sites, or using a Pokki App, the Pokki Menu, or any of our services or products, you consent to the transfer, storage and use of your information in the United States. 

9.     POLICY CHANGES

We may make changes to this policy from time to time. If we make material changes in the way we use personal information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our site or sending you an email and indicating the date of the latest changes to our policy. Users are bound by any changes to the Pokki Privacy Policy when he or she uses our site or services after such changes have been first posted, or in the case of substantial changes, 30 days upon posting those changes.

10.     CONTACT

Pokki, Inc. is the entity responsible for the processing of your personal information under this Pokki Privacy Policy.  Pokki, Inc is not responsible for the practices of any third party whose services and products you may use.  If you have feedback, questions or concerns about this Pokki Privacy Policy, contact us at Privacy, c/o Pokki, Inc., 510 Market St, Ste 301, San Diego, CA 92101 or email us at privacy@pokki.com.

Effective Date of this Pokki Privacy Policy:  July 9, 2013
